http://www.1800jeffers.com/pages/privacy-policy

menu
If animals could talk, they'd say Jeffers!
Vitamins & Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
Vaccines
Wormers (Dewormers)
Weight Control Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
Vitamins & Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
Vitamins & Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
Vitamins & Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
Vitamins & Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
Vitamins & Supplements
Wormers (Dewormers)
West Nile
Wormers (Dewormers)
Topical
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy.
Home
Free Shipping on most orders over $49!  Details
Privacy Policy
Jeffers Privacy PolicyYour trust is important to us. Jeffers strives to make your shopping experience as easy and secure as possible. This privacy policy is designed to review how we collect and use information you provide. Any questions or feedback are welcome.
Information we collect and how we use it:
We collect information about your visit to our site. If you enter your email address, opt-in to emails, or make a purchase we may collect personal and technical information about you, your visit, and your recent purchases. This may include email address, name, address, phone numbers, gender, order information, product interests, content topic, interests, loyalty information, customer number, etc. in addition to information about your visit such as IP Address, operating system, location information, and other device information. We may record additional information about your visit including the pages you viewed on the site/s, products you browsed, or placed in an online shopping cart as well as any content pages you have viewed. We collect this information about you and your preferences to create a profile of your interests and to serve you personalized content on websites and/or via personalized marketing promotions that we believe may be of interest to you. In some cases, we may automatically enroll you in marketing campaigns based on your product interests or past purchases.
You may voluntarily disclose additional personal information about yourself inside of a preference center or as part of a contest or sweepstakes, at a trade show, by taking a survey, contacting us by phone, or entering information into our website forms. By providing this additional personal information you authorize us to use this information in connection with personalized marketing promotions and interest-based advertising.
You may optionally rate or review a product by entering your email, a star rating, and short text. By providing your review you authorize us to disclose your endorsement to other shoppers interested in that product.You may also provide your name and address if you use curbside pickup at our retail location. This encrypted and will not be shared with 3rd parties outside the tool used to collect it. We may use the information internally to track customer usage, allocate additional budget or services, track the success of campaigns, or make marketing decisions for local retail customers.
In order to measure the performance of marketing campaigns we monitor actions you take in connection with our marketing campaigns including links clicked, order total, pages visited, and other relevant data. We use cookies to recognize you when you use or return to a site to provide a continuous, personalized shopping experience.
We use retargeting cookies and allow carefully screened 3rd party service providers to provide interest-based advertisements to you on this or other websites, or by direct mailing. We may also send direct mail if you have provided a mailing address. Some 3rd party companies have their own tracking technologies that we do not control.
If you use our "tell a friend" option on a product page or email, we will use their name and email address to deliver a one-time email message to them.
We may combine information we collect with other information you have disclosed or by using 3rd party services. This is used to better serve you with relevant products, services, content, or to improve our company.
We may disclose information as required by law, court orders, subpoenas, to 3rd parties in the course of an investigation, or to protect Jeffers or its customers from harm, fraud, or security threats. In addition, we may share information to investigate technical problems or threats, violations of terms and conditions, or to protect the integrity of the website.
Tracking Technology:
Jeffers uses standard tracking technology. Some of the technology we use to collect information include cookies, tags, pixels, and web beacons. Some of our 3rd party services use these technologies to collect information on our behalf. For example, we use Google Analytics to learn about our customer's interaction with the website.
Your Options:
You have the right to be removed from emails or direct mailings. You may unsubscribe directly from the email, or by contacting us. To opt out of direct mail, please contact us at 1-800-533-3377 or use the address at the end of this policy.
In addition, you may use your browser's tools to block storage of information. This may make many features unavailable, including cart and checkout. This is browser and device specific.
Jeffers does not have a "do not track" feature. By using this website, you are consenting to our practices and policies. You may be removed from internet-based advertising at http://optout.aboutads.info. This only impacts advertising networks that participate, such as Google, AOL and Yahoo. This is also browser and device specific. This service is operated independently and is beyond the control of Jeffers.
Additionally, we have links to outside websites that we deem helpful to you, the customer. We do not control any tracking or content of those websites.
Security Measures:
Jeffers uses reasonable and appropriate physical, administrative, and technical controls to protect your personal information. Our website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, the industry standard in transferring information when handling personal information. We do not store credit cards on our site, but we do pass it to our credit card processing company, which assigns it a token that we can use for payment settlements. Agents, contractors, and partners of Jeffers who have access to your personal information in connection with providing services for Jeffers are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are rendering for Jeffers.
Jeffers keeps personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.
Although Jeffers makes every effort to keep your data safe, data transmissions through the internet are not without risks. We take many precautions, but we cannot guarantee complete safety for this, or any other website. Please be advised, Jeffers will never request sensitive information through email.
Updating Your Information:
You may correct or update your information by visiting your account page. You may also request updates by contacting us using the contact section below. Yoy will be required to verify your identity to make such requests for information.
California Residents:
Residents of California who have an established relationship with Jeffers may request certain types of information about the personal information Jeffers has shared with its partners and 3rd parties. Additionally, Californians may request addresses of 3rd party companies we have shared information with during the last year. This is limited to one request each year. Please contact us in writing with the subject line or attention: "California Privacy Rights".
Governing Law:
Jeffers is based in the state of Alabama in the United States. Any dispute that arises will be governed by and construed under the statutes and laws of Alabama. This includes, but is not limited to, disputes about your personal information, privacy, contractual disputes, interaction, communications, or disputes resulting from the use of this website.
Children under 13:
Our site where this policy is found is intended for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child has given us information, you can email us at customerservice@jefferspet.com, or use the contact information below. Please use the subject line “Privacy Information Request" in written requests.
Privacy Policy Changes:
Please check this Privacy Policy periodically, as changes may occur at any time.
Contact Us:
If you have questions or comments about this policy, please contact us using the information below. If you need to correct, delete, or request copies of your information, please contact us using the subject line explained above.
Email: customerservice@jefferspet.com
Phone: 1-800-533-3377
Mailing address: Jeffers Privacy Compliance PO Box 100 Dothan, AL 36302
Help animals live longer, healthier lives.
Sign up today!
Receive special offers and promotions, and 10% off your first online purchase!
